Hey everyone! Welcome to a new video here in Hamburg at Innasectum with Julia.
Hi! Should I say Julia? I don't care. You don't care.
Okay so it's Julia, one of the Innasectum bosses.
And she's going to show me the store today and I'm going to try some outfits.
Yeah I'm going to try some outfits. I'm really curious because we have a long
history together at least from my side but I'll tell you more about it later. So I think we're
going to try some dresses. Yeah first outfit let's go. Yeah let's go. I think you might be a small
since our sizes are like very small we have to see if you're a small or a medium but usually
no that's fine. So this should work pretty well for you because you're
Yeah, tall as well. And that's my problem mostly.
But this is like, this goes under the knee. Okay, so yeah, it should work for you. Okay.
Okay, let's have a look. Careful, it's very slippery. Yeah, it's very slippery. What do you
think? It's perfect. It's pink. Yeah, it looks like a made to measure actually. It does, it does fit
It fits so good. If I turn around it fits everywhere.
That actually doesn't happen very often.
Because especially with latex somewhere it's better if it's custom made.
Probably. Because somewhere it's always a bit too loose or a bit too tight.
But well no. I can tell it fits perfectly.
It looks very good. I also like the pink on you.
I know. I hate that pink looks good on me.
But why it does?
Yeah I know but I don't like pink.
Oh. Too bad.
It's okay because it's combined with black.
So yeah.
Very nice.
I feel very good in it.
I can tell. Great.
So I went outside to take some pictures and some more videos because
it's lighter here and windy.
I know that you like this one very much, not me.
I still haven't gotten used to the color, but you mentioned something new, special.
Show it to me!
So, there we go.
Oh, it's black, I like it.
Black and gold.
Black and gold is a nice combination.
So yeah, it's a bra and choker.
Okay.
And I also have some like a high waisted panty.
Yes.
Okay.
This laser cut thing.
Oh, that looks really nice.
Yeah.
And I see you have like golden black eye makeup.
Yeah, my makeup is like perfect for this.
And I think this might look really good on you.
Okay, so I'm going to get changed.
Yes, let's go.
Tada, I'm back.
Yes, perfect.
I have to take a look actually.
Cool.
I'm too high. Or I'm too tall for a mirror.
Nice!
I like it.
Which one do you like better? The pink one or the gold one?
I like the pink one because it's a dress and I'm more fond of dresses than bras and stuff.
but the color combination here is better.
That's what I thought.
I have to admit.
And also I like the laser cut.
So is this the special laser cut design, a new one?
Yeah, this is the new one and this is going to be a very limited edition.
Every outfit can only be made like three times.
Some of them only twice.
Customers have to be fast.
Yes.
So you're the first one to try it on.
So thanks that you opened the store for me because it's not the official opening hours.
Yes, just to make sure we have enough time to try everything.
And also we're tested, we're vaccinated, we don't have to wear masks.
So I think especially for the video thing, that's a bit easier.
But yeah, I also have some leggings with the laser cut, but I fear it might be a little bit too short.
You can show them to me.
So there's the leggings.
leggings oh also it's the same design yeah a bit smaller but that would work with the bra oh it's
a high waisted one yeah and you think it's too short for me i i think so yeah yeah maybe a bit
i mean you can try it anyway but or maybe i'll try something different or you can try something
else but it's a cool design especially if you're not into panties yeah take the leggings instead
yeah of course i'm only showing female stuff because yeah obviously i am wearing it but
there's a lot of man fashion here as well so shirts for example with cool colors
so guys have a look as well
i switched back to the woman's side here because i'm going to pick an outfit now
Let's see.
I think I'll go for something military-stylish.
Maybe this one?
A blouse and then...
Yeah, I think this would work.
See ya!
So how do you like that one?
Good.
I'm not the typical military fan so I'm not really into the olive green but I like the
cut of it and I like the combination as a whole outfit.
So it looks really good and I think it fits us perfectly.
That's crazy because usually people don't really fit in the standard sizes but I think
I do.
You do.
It's so funny.
I mean I know your label is way older but we met in 2016.
Yes.
Because it was my first latex fashion show and I worked for InnoCentrum all these years
ago.
It was the second collection I made for Innocentum.
I think I started in 2014.
And I remember that you dressed me at the rehearsal for the show.
Yeah.
Yeah, you can take this and that.
And then I was like, okay, leggings, blouse, corset, everything.
Yeah, I remember.
And the evening, the show was also really cool.
Yeah.
It was a cool show.
I'm always so excited for shows.
Me too.
But yeah, it was a cool time.
Yeah, it was a cool time. So we know each other for quite a while.
Yeah, I think that's the first time we met, right?
Five years ago.
But I know that I'm going to try on one more thing.
And I think it's time for a latex corset.
Yeah, so we have everything. We have a dress, we have lingerie, we have military.
Two piece military and now it's corset.
Of course I had last outfit. Yes. And it does fit good as well. Yeah. Damn everything fits so good.
That's a really rare thing. Yeah. So because usually we have to take measurements and I think
most of our customers are made to measure. So you would recommend regular customers come here,
get your measurements taken. Yes. Made to measure catsuit, military outfit, whatever. Also if you
you don't have the possibility to come here you can always send us an email and
then I can mail you the measurement chart and you can just send us the
measurements. So definitely you do cat suits as well? We do everything.
So you can order anything on our website or anything you see
here. Which is a lot. But also if you have an own idea or any special wishes
you can tell us and we can make a custom design thing. So you as head of design would do it then.
So yeah, usually we can make every wish come true.
That's the best advertising slug.
But yeah, I do have to say I'm totally satisfied with everything I tried because everything fit, everything was comfortable and looked good and stuff like that.
So I can totally recommend that you guys come here and have a look in Hamburg.
If you're ever in Hamburg, stop by here.
Yes.
And take a look here and try things on, because it's cool.
Have a look at the website if you're not coming to Hamburg.
Yeah, or maybe if you're next year at the German Fetish Ball.
So you're at Fairtrades.
Yes.
Okay.
Definitely.
I hope so.
We do hope so.
As usual next year.
but you have an online shop as you said. We have an online shop as well. I'll link everything down below of course.
Also the homepage and stuff. And then I have to say thank you. Thank you for coming here.
Thank you for having me. It's so nice to see you again after like three years or two.
That's crazy. And thanks that you took the time for me. Of course. So now you're going to
help me undress again. One last time. And we say goodbye to you. Bye!